All right then gang, it has been a while in the making, but it is finally here.The Claude Code Masterclass, available now over on netninja.dev.The course is $15 to buy, but if you use the promo code ClaudeNinja, all one word, you can grab it at half price for just $7.50.Anyway, I've spent the last six or seven weeks putting this together, trying to pack in as much genuinely useful, practical content as possible, and I've really enjoyed making it.
好的，各位，這已經醞釀了好一段時間，但它終於來了。 Claude Code 大師課，現在在 netninja.dev 上架了。 課程售價 15 美元，但如果你使用促銷碼 ClaudeNinja（全部一個字）， 只需 7.5 美元即可半價購得。 無論如何，我花了過去六七週的時間製作這門課程， 試圖盡可能地塞入真正有用的實用內容，我真的很享受製作過程。
So whether you're completely new to Claude Code, you've been using it a little bit, but without any real structure or workflow, or even if you're slightly skeptical about AI tools in general, this course is built with you in mind.It's also not a vibe coding course.In my experience, AI is at its most powerful when it's paired with some coding experience and project knowledge, and that's the angle this course takes throughout.
無論你是完全不了解 Claude Code 的新手、 已經使用了一段時間但沒有真正的結構或工作流程， 或者你甚至對 AI 工具總體上有些懷疑， 這門課程都是為你而建的。 這也不是一門「氛圍編程」課程。 根據我的經驗，AI 在搭配程式設計經驗和專案知識時最為強大， 這正是這門課程貫穿始終的角度。
Anyway, we start off with the fundamentals, and that means getting Claude Code installed and set up properly, going through some key settings and commands, and then dropping it into a real project to analyze an existing code base and start making changes.From there, we dig into how to manage context effectively, how Claude's tools work under the hood, and how permissions are handled, and how to create custom commands for the kinds of tasks that you're going to be doing all the time.
無論如何，我們從基礎開始：正確安裝和設定 Claude Code、 介紹一些關鍵設定和指令， 然後將其導入一個真實專案，分析現有程式碼庫並開始進行修改。 從那裡，我們深入探討如何有效管理上下文、 Claude 的工具在底層如何運作、如何處理權限， 以及如何為你將一直執行的各種任務建立自訂指令。
We also take a proper look at hooks, including building our own hook to automatically format code whenever Claude code edits a file, so it fits neatly into a real-world workflow.Once we've covered the basics, we'll move on to a spec-driven development workflow that I use all the time now in my own projects, and to do that, we'll be using a mixture of custombands, clawed codes, planning mode, and extended thinking with the Opus model to implement new features in a structured way.It's a simple three-step workflow that keeps me firmly in the loop.
我們也會深入了解 Hooks，包括建立我們自己的 Hook， 讓 Claude Code 每次編輯檔案時自動格式化程式碼，整齊地融入真實世界的工作流程。 涵蓋基礎知識後，我們將進入一個規格驅動的開發工作流程， 這是我現在在自己的專案中一直使用的方式。 為此，我們將混合使用自訂指令、Claude Code 的規劃模式， 以及結合 Opus 模型的延伸思考，以結構化的方式實作新功能。 這是一個讓我穩固掌握迴圈的簡單三步驟工作流程。
It lets me review every code change and then jump into the weeds to make manual edits whenever I want.And honestly, I think that level of control is essential if you're going to be using AI as part of your development cycle.After that, we'll look at MCP servers and how they let Claude code interact with things outside of your codebase.In particular, we'll use the Figma MCP server to pull in design information and a Firebase server to communicate directly with a backend.Then we'll move on to skills.
它讓我可以審查每一個程式碼變更，並在我想要時深入研究進行手動編輯。 坦白說，我認為如果你要將 AI 作為開發週期的一部分，這種程度的掌控是必不可少的。 之後，我們將看看 MCP 伺服器，以及它們如何讓 Claude Code 與程式碼庫之外的事物互動。 具體來說，我們會使用 Figma MCP 伺服器引入設計資訊， 並使用 Firebase 伺服器直接與後端通訊。 然後我們將進入 Skills（技能）。
which let us bake in more predictable patterns and outcomes by essentially teaching Claude how to do certain things in a specific preferred way.So that might be how schemas and data models are created or how database queries are structured, that kind of thing.On top of that, we'll do a proper deep dive into sub-agents and how they can improve your workflow using isolated context windows.and by running tasks in parallel.
Skills 讓我們能夠烘培出更可預測的模式和結果， 本質上是在教導 Claude 如何以特定的偏好方式做某些事情。 例如，如何建立 Schema 和資料模型，或如何架構資料庫查詢，諸如此類。 除此之外，我們還將對子代理進行深入探討， 了解它們如何透過隔離的上下文視窗和並行運行任務來改善你的工作流程。
We'll also be making three sub-agents of our own, which are gonna fit nicely into that spec-driven workflow that we set up in the course.And while we're learning all of this, we'll be building a project called PocketHeist, which is designed to add a little bit of mischief to the workplace.The idea is that coworkers can assign each other little heists around the office using secret code names.It's a full little project, but it also gives us a solid, realistic app to demonstrate the benefits of using Claude code as we build it out.
我們還會製作三個我們自己的子代理， 它們將很好地融入我們在課程中設定的規格驅動工作流程。 在學習這一切的同時，我們將建立一個叫做 PocketHeist 的專案， 旨在為工作場所增添一點惡作劇色彩。 這個想法是讓同事可以使用秘密代號相互分配辦公室裡的小任務。 這是一個完整的小專案，也給了我們一個紮實、真實的應用程式， 在建立過程中示範使用 Claude Code 的好處。
And once the core functionality and design of the application are all in place, we're going to bring GitHub into the workflow as well, and we'll use the Claude GitHub app to automatically review pull requests and have it work independently on open issues.After that, we'll deploy the app to VSL and set up automatic deployments whenever the production branch updates.
一旦應用程式的核心功能和設計都就位， 我們也會將 GitHub 引入工作流程， 並使用 Claude GitHub 應用程式自動審查拉取請求， 並讓它獨立處理開放的 Issues。 之後，我們將應用程式部署到 Vercel，並設定在生產分支更新時自動部署。
On top of all of that, we'll take a look at a slightly newer tool, the Claude code for the web tool, which lets us spin up tasks remotely in the cloud and open pull requests directly on GitHub without running anything locally.And again, we're gonna be doing all of this in a structured, refined way that fits nicely into a development workflow.Not vibe coding, not one-shotting the whole application, but instead using Claude code to make us 10 times more productive.
除此之外，我們還會看看一個相對較新的工具：網頁版 Claude Code 工具， 它讓我們可以在雲端遠端啟動任務，並直接在 GitHub 上建立拉取請求， 無需在本地執行任何東西。 同樣，我們將以結構化、精練的方式做這一切，很好地融入開發工作流程。 不是氛圍編程，不是一口氣完成整個應用程式， 而是使用 Claude Code 讓我們的生產力提升 10 倍。
So whether you're completely new to Claude Code and Agentic Coding, or if you have some experience with it but haven't really figured out how to fit it nicely into your own workflow, or even if you're an AI skeptic, then this course is designed for you.It's packed full of tips, tricks, and things that I've learned over the last year since its release, and it's going to put you in a much better position to harness the power of AI in your own projects.
無論你是完全不了解 Claude Code 和代理式編程的新手， 還是已有一些經驗但還沒真正想清楚如何融入自己的工作流程， 甚至你是個 AI 懷疑論者，這門課程都是為你設計的。 它充滿了我在過去一年發布以來學到的技巧、竅門和心得， 將讓你在自己的專案中更好地利用 AI 的力量。
So again, use the promo code CLAUDENINJA to get the course for half price, just $7.50, but that code's only available for the next few weeks.After that, it's goingbe full price of $15, which is still less than most courses sell for to be honest.So I'll leave the link to this course down below the video.
所以再次提醒，使用促銷碼 CLAUDENINJA 可以半價獲得課程，只需 7.5 美元， 但這個代碼只有接下來幾週有效。 之後將恢復全價 15 美元，老實說這已經比大多數課程的售價要低了。 所以我會在影片下方留下這門課程的連結。
Or if you want access to my entire library of masterclass courses and pro exclusive shorter courses not found anywhere else, you can sign up for a NetNinja membership and get instant access to all of them including this brand new Claude Code Masterclass as well.That's just $9 a month and you can even get your first month half price by using this promo code right here.So again, I'll leave a link to the pro membershippage below the video as well.Anyway, I really, really hope you enjoyed the course.
或者，如果你想存取我的完整大師課程庫和在其他地方找不到的 Pro 獨家短期課程， 你可以報名 NetNinja 會員，立即存取所有課程， 包括這個全新的 Claude Code 大師課。 每月只需 9 美元，使用這裡的促銷碼第一個月甚至可以享半價優惠。 所以我也會在影片下方留下 Pro 會員頁面的連結。 無論如何，我真的真的希望你喜歡這門課程。
I've had loads of fun making it and I'm going to see you all in the next one.
製作過程非常有趣，下個系列見。